

# **ASKER HAMZA**

# **Graphic Designer**



+971 5 0202 6590



askerm4u@gmail.com

DESIGN SKILLS	)
Adobe Photoshop	
Adobe Illustrator	
CorelDraw	
Adobe Premier	
Adobe After Effects	
Adobe Dimension	
Autodesk 3ds Max	
SketchUp	
Drawing/illustration	

# **PROFILE**

I am an enthusiastic and dedicated professional. With five years of experience in the advertising agency, taking on tasks and assignments with passion, creativity, reliability, and organization, I am looking to take on the role of Graphic Designer / junior Web designer. I believe that this will offer me greater opportunities to unleash my potential to the maximum.

& in HTML and Web Administration

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS









#### **EDUCATION**



**Diploma in Multimedia-Editing & Special Effects** from IHT Collage of media studies,
Tirur, Kerala, India

**+2** Higher Secondary Education Board Kerala, India

SSLC Dept. of General Education, Kerala, India

# WORK EXPERIENCE



2021-2024

# **Graphic Designer**

Vega Digital IT Solution Dubai

2020-2021

# **Graphic Designer**

SV Colour Graphic Bangalore

2016-2018

# Lead Graphic Designer

Maxpro Technologies Pvt. Ltd India

# PERSONAL DETAILS



Date of Birth : 20-01-1988

Nationality : Indian

Marital Status : Married

#### **HOBBIES & INTEREST**



Reading



Traveling